1a) Define a function to convert a temperature expressed in Fahrenheit degrees into Celsius degrees. Your function must not prompt the user for the input fahrenheit temperature. Instead, it must accept the fahrenheit input as a parameter and use that input in your code. The resulting Celsius temperature must be displayed (printed out) to the user.
1b) Define a function to convert a temperature expressed in Celsius degrees into Fahrenheit degrees. Your function must not prompt the user for the input Celsius temperature. Instead, it must accept the Celsius input as a parameter and use that input in your code. The resulting Fahrenheit temperature must be displayed (printed out) to the user.
2) Define a function that accepts an input year parameter and determines whether it is a leap year or not.
3)Based on what you already learned, write a python program that you feel happy about (if not proud of). If you can't find a topic, you can take the example used in the lecture, write a program that does similar things: allowing people to query some info that is already in the program "database" and allow them to amend the database in certain ways.
  Write the program in a self-explanatory manner. That is, a user can use the program directly without having to read the code to understand it.