1) Write a function that takes an integer number as an input and returns a string with each digit converted to the corresponding English word (e.g., 42 -> four two, NOT forty two). Write a short set of test cases for the function.
2) Write a function that takes 1 input parameter and displays an left-sided right-angled triangle (this means the 90 degree angle is on the bottom left side as shown below) whose base and height are equal to the input parameter. The display format must only use the star (*) symbol.
3) Write a function that takes 2 input parameters and displays a table of numbers according to the following format;
4) The  Collatz Conjecture (or 3n+1 conjecture) says that if you repeat the process of HOTPO to any natural number, it always comes back to 1. HOTPO means halve-or-tripple-plut-one, the process simply means this;


